2;Básico;Can / Can't;|Complete the dialogue: 
Sandra: "__________ speak French?" 
Thomas: "No, _______________."|;Can you/I can't;You can/I can't;Can you/I can;You can/can't I
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Fill in the gap with the correct alternative: "__________ help me here, please? These boxes are too heavy.";Can you;Are you;You can;I need
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Which of the following alternatives is incorrect?: " _______________ see the sea from my apartment. _______________ see it from yours?";I can/You can;I can't/Can you;I can/Can't you;I can/Can you
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the best alternative: "_______________ help me? I __________ find this street on the map.";Can you/can't;Can you/can;Can't you/can;You can/can't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "She is a very good teacher. She __________ help you with that.";can;can't;can to;to can
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Which of the following answers is incorrect?: "Can you bring me some water on your way back?" ;"I guess it's nice.";"Yes, sure.";"Sorry, I'm not coming back.";"Ice water?"
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the best option to complete the dialogue: "Can you help me take these books upstairs?";"Of course.";"Sure, I can't.";"Yes, I do.";"I'm going to call him."
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "________________ use your cell phone for a second please? I need to call my mom.";Can I;Do I;Can you;I can
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the best alternative: "John can __________ seven languages.";speak;speaks;to speak;speaking
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "Excuse me, ______________ have a glass of water, please?";can I;I can't;I can;do I
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "I'm sorry, _______________ talk to you right now. She's on a phone call.";she can't;can she;can't she;she can
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "I can drive, but _______________ ride a motorcycle." ;I can't;I can;can I;can
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ use your phone charger, please?";Can I;I can;I can't;Can
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "Sometimes in stories, _______________.";animals can speak;can animals speak;do animals speak;can't animals speak
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Which of the following sentences is correct?;"Can I call you right now?";"I can call you right now?";"I can't call you right now?";"Can I call you right now."
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "Oh no, _______________ remember where I left my keys.";I can't;I can;can I;can't I
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the best alternative: "Cats __________ climb trees but __________ fly.";can/can't;doesn't/can't;can't/can;don't/can't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "__________ dogs swim?";Can;Are there;Is there;What
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "Birds __________ fly and sing.";can;can't;doesn't;don't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;|Complete the dialogue:
Sandra: "Where __________ I buy stamps?"
Mark: "At the post office."|;can;can't;doesn't;does
2;Básico;Can / Can't;|Complete the dialogue:
Sue: "__________ you ride horses?"
John: "No, I __________."|;Can/can't;Does/can't;Can/can;Can/doesn't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "Have you seen my bag? I __________ find it anywhere!";can't;can;don't;doesn't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "__________ you call me again? I __________ hear you!";Can/can't;Can/can;Do/can't;Does/can
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct answer: "Ann's got the job because she __________ speak three languages.";can;can't;don't;doesn't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;|Complete the dialogue:
Ted: "__________ you come to my party on Friday?"
Sarah: "No, I'm sorry, we __________."|;Can/can't;Do/can't;Can/can;Does/can't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "This hotel room is amazing! I __________ see the mountains from the window!";can;can't;don't;doesn't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "Hello? _______________ hear me? My cell phone is not working very well.";Can you;You can;You can't;Are you
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "I think I'm in love, _______________ stop thinking of her.";I can't;I can;can't;can I
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ ask you a personal question? Are you married?";Can I;I can;I can't;Do I
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ to the movies with you. I have to study a lot tonight.";I can't go;I can go;Can't go;I don't go
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ believe you don't like chocolate, I love it!";I can't;I can;I am not;Can I
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "I'm sorry if it's not a good time but _______________ help me with this contract?";can your brother;he can;can him;you brother can
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "I'm sorry, I _______________ you very well. _______________ say it again, please?";can't hear/Can you;can't hear/You can;can hear/You;can't hear/You
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "Some things __________ be explained. They are inexplicable.";cannot;don't;can;could
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ smoke here, but you __________ smoke outside.";You can't/can;You can't/can't;You can/can;Can't you/can
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ play volleyball? I __________ play any sports.";Can you/can't;You can/can't;He can't/can;He can/I can't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "Our daughter is ill, so we _______________ come to your birthday party tonight. I'm sorry.";can't;can;to can;could
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ speak louder, please? I _______________ hear you.";Can you/can't;Can you/can;You can/can't;You can't/can't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ open the door for me, please? These boxes are very heavy.";Can you;You can;You can't;Can I
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ try a bit of your cake? It smells really good.";Can I;I can't;You can;Can you
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "Do you have a dictionary to lend me? I __________ understand this word.";can't;can;can not;could
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct answer: "_______________ use your phone, please? I have to call my mother.";Can I;Do I;Don't I;I can
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "It's cold, so the children __________ go to the beach today. They are going to get sick.";can't;can;do;must
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "I __________ open the door because I don't have the key.";can't;can;do;must
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct answer: "Kelly __________ work in the garden today because it's raining.";can't;can;doesn't;must
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "Tom __________ use my computer today because it's out of battery.";can't;can;doesn't;must
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "You __________ water the plants three times a day. It's bad for them.";can't;can;doesn't;must
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "__________ I go out with my friends tonight? We are going to a nightclub in town.";Can;Do;Did;Didn't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct answer: "On Fridays the children __________ bring their toys to school. They have lots of fun!";can;couldn't;could;didn't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "My baby is 1 month old. He __________ walk yet.";can't;can;could;must
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "Matt __________ go swimming because it is very cold.";can't;can;could;couldn't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;|Complete the dialogue: 
William: "__________ we have ice cream for dessert?"
Mrs. Smith: "Yes, you ___________."|;Can/can;Can/can't;Can/don't;Can/couldn't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct answer: "Zebras __________ climb trees, but they __________ run very fast.";can't/can;can/can't;can/can;can't/doesn't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "Elephants __________ swim, but they __________ climb trees.";can/can't;can/can;doesn't/can't;can't/doesn't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "Dogs __________ speak, but they __________ bark.";can't/can;can/can;can't/can't;can/can't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;|Complete the dialogue: 
Mark: "How many languages __________ you speak?"
Ann: "I can speak 3 languages: Portuguese, Spanish, and English."|;can;can't;could;couldn't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct answer: "You usually __________ take pictures inside museums.";can't;must;could;couldn't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "People __________ read books at libraries.";can;can't;mustn't;couldn't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "I'm going to take guitar lessons because _______________ play the guitar very well.";I can't;can I;I do;can't I
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "_______________ see the menu? I want to check out the prices.";Can I;Do I;I can;I can't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct answer: "Mike is going to take swimming lessons because he __________ swim very well.";can't;can;do;does
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "There is a very nice store in 5th Avenue. You __________ find something nice there.";can;can't;don't;mustn't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "She has lived in France for 10 years, so she __________ speak French very well.";can;can't;doesn't;mustn't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "__________ you give me directions to the mall? I want to go shopping.";Can;Do;Don't;Mustn't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct answer: "There are many countries where women __________ vote. We have to change that.";can't;can;do;could
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "Batman is a superhero that __________ fly.";can't;could;couldn't;mustn't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "If the weather is good, _______________ ride your bike to school.";you can;you can't;you cannot;can you
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "I_________ go swimming this week because I'm sick.";can't;can;don't;do
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ play any instrument? _______________ play the guitar.";Can you/I can;You can/I can;Can you/Can I;You can/I can't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ play any sports?";Can your children;Your children can;Your children can't;Your children don't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "_______________ write with your left hand?";Can you ;You can;You;You can't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "I __________ cook pasta, but I __________ cook meat. I'm a vegetarian.";can/can't;can/can;can't/can't;can't/can
2;Básico;Can / Can't;|Complete the dialogue:
Bruce: "______________ surf?"
Amy: "No, _______________."|;Can you/I can't;You can/I can't;Can you/I can;You can't/I can't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "Where _______________ smoke?";can we;we can;we can't;we
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ help me in the garden?";Can't you;You can't;You can;You
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "This neighborhood is very peaceful. _______________ hear the birds singing?";Can you;You can;You can't;You
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "_______________ understand French?";Can you;You can;You can't;You
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ stay with my brother while we're in London. He'll be happy to have us.";We can;We can't;Can't we;Can we
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ hand me the pen, please? I need to sign this contract.";Can you;You can;Can't you;You can't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "______________ cross the road when the light is red.";You can't;You can;Can't you;Can you
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "_______________ help me find the documents, please?";Can you;You can;You;You can't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "I know her, but I __________ remember her name.";can't;can;do;am not
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "The president __________ talk to you right now. He's busy.";can't;can;don't;isn't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "I __________ travel with you next month because I don't have any money.";can't;can;don't;do
2;Básico;Can / Can't;|Complete the dialogue: 
Student: "Do I have to use a pencil?"
Teacher: "No, you __________ use a pen, if you prefer."|;can;can't;do;don't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;|Complete the dialogue:
Secretary: "Mr. Anderson is out of the office right now."
Bryan: "OK, _______________ leave a message?"|;can I;I can;I can't;I do
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "Excuse me, _______________ take a picture of us, please?";can you;you can;you can't;you
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ discuss this later? I'm really busy right now.";Can we;We can;We can't;We
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ turn the volume down, please? _______________ concentrate on my work.";Can you/I can't;You can/I can't;You can/I can;Can you/I can
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "_______________ close the door, please? It's very cold in here.";Can you;You can;You do;You
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "_______________ switch on the light? It's dark in here.";Can I;I can;Do you;You don't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ believe I forgot to bring my camera. Look at all these beautiful places.";I can't;I can ;Can I;Can't I
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "My brother __________ surf, but he __________ swim.";can't/can;can't/can't;can/can;do/don't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "My sister __________ swim a hundred meters in 1 minute. That's really fast!";can;can't;doesn't;don't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the question: "_______________ start a fire without a match? It's very hard.";Can you;You can;You can't;You
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "Paul doesn't want to go on the boat trip because he __________ swim.";can't;can;don't;isn't
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ have dinner with us tonight if you want. I'll cook.";You can;Can you;You can't;Can't you
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ go to the museum today. It's closed.";We can't;We can;Can we;Can't we
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "_______________ borrow my jacket if you like.";You can;You can't;Can you;You
2;Básico;Can / Can't;Complete the sentence: "Some people __________ speak more than four languages. I find it amazing.";can;can't;don't;cannot
